{
    "subject": "resource/\u015eehzade_Mehmed",
    "predicate": "ontology/parent",
    "object": "resource/Suleiman_the_Magnificent",
    "human_readable": "\u015eehzade Mehmed is a child of Suleiman the Magnificent.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7801287174224854,
            "question": "Who is \u015eehzade Mehmed's father?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6901453733444214,
            "question": "Who were some of \u015eehzade Mehmed's siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6386151909828186,
            "question": "What is known about \u015eehzade Mehmed's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5649181008338928,
            "question": "Is Suleiman the Magnificent known for anything specific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5119945406913757,
            "question": "What was Suleiman the Magnificent's title?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4558506906032562,
            "question": "Were any of \u015eehzade Mehmed's other family members influential figures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34504464268684387,
            "question": "How did \u015eehzade Mehmed contribute to history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31033626198768616,
            "question": "What legacy did Suleiman the Magnificent leave behind?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3027035593986511,
            "question": "During what period did Suleiman the Magnificent rule?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.299122154712677,
            "question": "What was the Ottoman Empire like during Suleiman the Magnificent's reign?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=\u015eehzade Mehmed is a child of Suleiman the Magnificent.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7685_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=During what period did Suleiman the Magnificent rule?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7685_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What legacy did Suleiman the Magnificent leave behind?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7685_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did \u015eehzade Mehmed contribute to history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7685_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7685_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7685_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7685_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7685_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7685_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7685_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7685_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7685_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7685_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7685_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that suggests \u015eehzade Mehmed's father was Sultan Suleiman the Magnificent, and his mother was Hurrem Sultan, one of Suleiman's consorts and legal wife. This supports the triple that \u015eehzade Mehmed is a child of Suleiman the Magnificent."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports \u015eehzade Mehmed being a son of Suleiman the Magnificent. For instance, the document at path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7685/re-ranker-msmarco/49.txt` states \"Mehmed was born in 1521, presumably around September, as the son of Sultan Suleiman and his concubine, H\u00fcrrem.\" Additionally, other documents mention Mehmed being a favored son and receiving special attention from Suleiman."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}